eaglecar.ca 2013-03-23

# EAGLE CANADA CAR RENTAL ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

                                                                                                YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS
                                                                                                Online Privacy Policy 2011
EAGLE CANADA CAR RENTAL ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy sets out how Eagle uses and protects any information that you give Eagle Canada Car Rental when
you use this website.
Eagle Canada Car Rental is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain
information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in
accordance with this privacy statement.
Eagle may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to
ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from June 1st 2011.
WHAT WE COLLECT
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
•        Name
•        Contact information including email address, telelphone numbers
•        Credit Card Information (Strictly for Reservation Transaction Purposes only)
•        demographic information preferences and interests for newsletters, specials
•        other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the
following reasons:
•        Internal record keeping.
•        We may use the information to improve our products and services.
•        We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information
which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
•        From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
         We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the web
site according to your interests.
SECURITY
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we
have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we
collect online.
HOW WE USE COOKIES
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is
added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web
applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and
dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and
improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes
and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and
which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the
data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually
modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the
website.
CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
•        whenever you are asked to ﬁll in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
•        if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you
may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@eaglecar.ca
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are
required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties
which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Canadian Personal Information
Protection and Electronic Documents Act Bill C-6 1999. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is
incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct
any information found to be incorrect.
